Branden Daniel Ng

Front-End Web Developer Melbourne, VIC

linkedin.com/in/brandendaniel in

Web Portfolio - branden.vercel.app

github.com/BrandenDaniel 🖸

J 04 32 375 587

Experienced front-end web developer with a fire passion for transforming static wireframes into interactive, beautiful spaced websites. Throughout my journey, I've had the privilege to collaborate with a diverse range of clients and businesses. I am currently learning React.js and API integrations.

Work Experience

LeasePLUS Group - SafeCode

Sept. 2022 - Present Melbourne CBD, VIC

Front-end Web Developer

SafeCode, a LeasePLUS subsidiary, creates novated leasing and salary packaging interfaces for individuals and businesses. With 100,000+ users, they cater to diverse clients across Australia.

Worked on proprietary leasing/salary packaging software for LeasePlus Group

• Management of all LeasePlus group's websites/portals (over 5+)

LeasePLUS Group - SalaryPackagingPLUS

Account Officer

Apr. 2022 - Sept. 2022 Melbourne CBD, VIC

Arcadian Digital & Sept. 2019 — Feb. 2020 Melbourne CBD. VIC

Junior Front-end Web Developer

As a bespoke digital and marketing agency, Arcadian deliver tailored solutions to organisations of all sizes. I worked with extremely talented engineers during my time there.

· Collaborative work with project managers and lead/senior developers

Build and structure WordPress child themes

Build and maintian company's own WordPress plugins and themes

Bebble Media & May. 2018 — Jun. 2019 North Laverton, VIC

Junior Front-end Web Developer

Tech Stack & Skills

A small digital agency in West Melbourne with in-house designers and developers.

Specialising in WordPress, they assist small business owners in expanding their ecommerce and online presence.

· Collaborate with web/graphic designers to reach mockup standards

- Integrations of plugins + customisation of plugins to suit client's specifics
- Manipulation of software styles (i.e plugins, themes) exact to design mockups

HTML JavaScript CSS Sass React ETFs & Index Funds Personal Finance Tech iQuery **Bootstrap** Git Azure deployment Critically Acclaimed Films Youtube Work/Projects My Web Portfolio 🔗 2023 MySalPack (employee portal) & 2023 React, JavaScript, HTML, CSS (Sass) JavaScript, ¡Query, Sass, Blazor, Bootstrap MySalPack (employer portal) & 2019 2022

2019

JavaScript, jQuery, Sass, Blazor, Bootstrap Spinach &

Kader Boot Co. Ø

Interests & Hobbies

PHP (WordPress), Sass, jQuery

CSS, HTML, jQuery

2018

PHP (WordPress), Sass, jQuery

Education

Udacity

Front End Web Developer Nanodegree

Online

Team Treehouse

Oct. 2017 - May 2018 Online

Front End Web Development Track

May - Aug. 2017

RMIT University

Melbourne, VIC Jul. 2016 - Apr. 2017

Completed 48 credits towards a Bachelor of Information Technology Relevant Courses Included:

- Web Programming
- · User-centered Design